This video is to showcase the analytics
feature newly implemented on LPShares website.
So to assess it, you just need
to go to your listings page,
that's the page with all your listings and
then you can go to an individual listing.
And then you see this analytics
tab which is now displayed for you
and the data is private to you and it's
collected from the 10th of June 2025.
Though if your listing has
been shared via a campaign,
then all of that data will also be displayed here.
So this analytics tab, it shows you all the views
on your listing, all the document
requests, all the bids received,
and all the shares for your listing.
So you can now see all of that private to you.
So I'll show you the feature in action.
So I'll go to a different user
On a different browser and
I'll search for that listing.
Then I'll view it.
So now that I've viewed
the listing, if I go back to the owner
of the listing and I refresh the page.
So as you can see, the total
views has increased by one.
The same thing if I make a bid
On that listing So once that is successful
And coming back to the original
Page, that's for the owner.
I refresh it, so as you can see, the
bids received has increased to 2.
So that's how it works, same thing for
document requests and same thing for shares.
i'll showcase shares.
Let's go back to that listing.
And now I viewed it again, but
this won't count as a new view,
so it is we're only counting the unique views.
So we're tracking it per session.
So since this is still the same session,
the view counts will remain the same,
but if I were to close the browser and
restart it, then it'll count as a new view.
So to showcase this share.
So I want to share it on Twitter.
So if I go back And I refresh the page.
So as you can see, the shares has
increased to 6 by 1.
So all of that data,
you know, collected on your listing is now
displayed to you also on the dashboard.
It now displays the total listing views.
So this is all your listings,
all the views are accumulated.
So that's what displays here.
I have just one published listing, but if I had
multiple and they all get some different views,
then you can get our data here.
So that's the analytics feature
on LP shares.
Thank you.